#### Contact

San Francisco, CA erickvivas.ng@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/erickvivas415 (LinkedIn) github.com/erickvivas415 (Portfolio)

## Top Skills

Financial Responsibilities
Affluent
Critical Thinking

# Languages

Español (Native or Bilingual)
Ingles (Native or Bilingual)
Cantonese (Elementary)
Korean (Elementary)

### Certifications

Principles of Cloud Computing I

Series 6 - Investment Company and Variable Contracts Products Representative

Communicating & Leading with Influence

The Asana Project Management Certificate

The Beginners Guide to Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence

# **Erick Vivas**

I lead teams to success, my philosophy revolves around fostering a client-centric environment, instilling in my staff the importance of delivering personalized, comprehensive financial solutions.

San Francisco Bay Area

# Summary

With over 5 years of experience in finance and over 10 years as an entrepreneur, I have been able to build a wealth of knowledge that helps me lead my team to success. I love to learn for myself and to help others. I believe we can always get better and grow to be better humans and professionals.

My passion for technology and data analysis helps me to understand and find solutions to innovate in any field.

# Experience

JPMorgan Chase Bank N. A.

6 years 4 months

Branch Manager

February 2022 - Present (2 years 10 months)

San Francisco, California, United States

#### Private Client Banker

January 2020 - February 2022 (2 years 2 months)

San Francisco Bay Area

### Relationship Banker

August 2018 - January 2020 (1 year 6 months)

San Francisco, California, United States

### Vivas Projects

**CEO** 

February 2021 - Present (3 years 10 months)

San Francisco, California, United States

Developing software that finds solutions to everyday problems.

Limon Rotisserie Office Manager March 2018 - August 2018 (6 months)

San Francisco Bay Area

Take care of Payroll, Inventory, Petty cash, Hiring Process, Insurance, Reservations.

Yoga Venezuela

**CEO** 

July 2015 - August 2018 (3 years 2 months)

Caracas Venezuela

Promover actividades relacionas con el Yoga y acroyoga en Venezuela y Manejo de la cuenta Yoga Venezuela en las redes sociales

Running Venezuela

CEO

December 2013 - August 2018 (4 years 9 months)

Venezuela

Blog sobre el running en Venezuela y el Mundo

Corporacion Nueva Genesis, C.A.

8 years 2 months

Director general

October 2010 - August 2018 (7 years 11 months)

Propietario

July 2010 - August 2018 (8 years 2 months)

Impulsar el crecimiento de Corporacion Nueva Genesis, C.A a traves de la creacion, implementacion y constante mejoramiento de una estructura basada en un servicio de primera a los clientes actuales y futuros de la compañia.

Rafys Pizza

Social Media Consultant

May 2017 - May 2018 (1 year 1 month)

Petaluma, California

Javalencia Cafe

Social Media Consultant

April 2017 - January 2018 (10 months)

Bahía de San Francisco y alrededores, Estados Unidos

Tucar Tours, C.A

Director de Operaciones

July 2015 - February 2017 (1 year 8 months)

Caracas Venezuela

Tucar tours ofrece servicios para corredores desde el manejo de planes para viajar y competir en Maratones como New York y Boston.

Inversiones Binacom, C.A

Gerente

November 2010 - January 2017 (6 years 3 months)

Actividades en el proceso de compra, manejo de personal, manejo de vitrina y control de precios.

Mandala Yoga Estudio
Profesor de yoga
January 2016 - December 2016 (1 year)

Calle el limón, Qta Los Cerezos Piso 2, El Cafetal

Clases de Vinyasa Power Yoga Secuencias Básicas e intermedias. Meditaciones al inicio y fin de cada clase. Guía para que los practicantes aprendan las posturas con una correcta alineación de forma segura.

Unicron System, C.A Director General October 2005 - June 2010 (4 years 9 months)

Manejo general de la compañía en todas sus áreas.

PC Standing, C.A
Director General
October 2005 - April 2007 (1 year 7 months)

Me desempeñe como director general de la compañía supervisando y realizando funciones en el departamento de compras y ventas corporativas.

Universidad Central de Venezuela Pasante de Informatica Escuela de Ingenieria January 2003 - January 2005 (2 years 1 month)

Mantenimiento de equipos informaticos y soporte a usuarios

# Education

Coding Dojo

Software Engineer, Software Engineer Full Stack Python · (August 2021 - March 2022)

### Universidad Central de Venezuela

Ingenieria Electrica · (1998 - 2006)

# All You Can Yoga

200 Hr RYT Power Vinyasa Yoga Teacher, Formación de profesores de yoga/ Terapia de yoga · (2015 - 2015)

### Social Media Tech

Social Media Avanzado · (2015 - 2015)

ACIEDIS. Asociación Internacional de Especialistas en Dinámica Grupal

Terapia en Constelaciones Familiares, Terapia · (2008 - 2009)